YTM NEWS LIVE BROADCAST
[EXCLUSIVE] THE UGLY TRUTH
BEHIND ENTERTAINMENT MOGUL LEE DAE-HO
YTM LIVE NEWS BROADCAST
[EXCLUSIVE] THE UGLY TRUTH
BEHIND ENTERTAINMENT MOGUL LEE DAE-HO
PUBLISH REQUEST SENT!
FINALE
[EXCLUSIVE] THE UGLY TRUTH
BEHIND ENTERTAINMENT MOGUL LEE DAE-HO
7 YEARS OF CORRUPTION
TIED TO BORROWED-NAME PROPERTY
EUNSEONG GROUP CHAIRMAN LEE DAE-HO
ARRESTED FOR ILLEGAL PE FUND
CHAIRMAN LEE DAE-HO ARRESTED
IS THIS THE FALL OF EUNSEONG GROUP?
TURMOIL IN THE EUNSEONG FAMILY,
ALL EYES ON WHO WILL TAKE CONTROL
LIM HYEON-JUN, SIGNATURE
[EUNSEONGILBO] RECRUITMENT NOTICE
[EUNSEONGILBO] RECRUITMENT NOTICE:
SERIA TEMPORARY ASSIGNMENT
REPORTER WI JEONG-SIN
LIM HYEON-JUN & WI JEONG-SIN
CHAIRMAN LEE DAE-HO ARRESTED ON CHARGES OF
MONEY LAUNDERING, SOLICITING MURDER…
GWON SE-NA
AIDE WOO YOUNG-SUK
CHAIRMAN LEE DAE-HO
CHAIRMAN LEE DAE-HO, AIDE WOO YOUNG-SUK
LIM HYEON-JUN
LIM HYEON-JUN & WI JEONG-SIN
GOOD DETECTIVE KANG PIL-GU 5
LIM HYEON-JUN & GWON SE-NA
ALREADY CUT TIES WITH CHAIRMAN LEE DAE-HO
AGENCY SHARES DONATED
TO CHILDREN'S CHARITY
KANG PIL-GU SEASON 5
VIEWERSHIP RATINGS
RATINGS EXCEED 20%
A TRIUMPHANT FINALE
A SLOW START,
BUT SOARS TO 20.6%!
THE KANG PIL-GU CREW
IS REWARDED PAID VACATION AGAIN!!
KANG PIL-GU 5 CONCLUDES
WITH RECORD RATINGS
GOOD DETECTIVE KANG PIL-GU 5
AT NUNGNAE STATION
A PLACE WHERE LONGING GATHERS LIKE SNOW
AND TENDER GREETINGS GATHER
LIKE AUTUMN LEAVES
REPORTER WI JEONG-SIN
WI JEONG-SIN
LIM HYEON-JUN
HOW ARE YOU? THE WEATHER IS NICE HERE.
COME BACK SOON.
I WENT TO THE HANGANG RIVER TODAY.
I MISS YOU.
EVERYTHING'S OKAY, RIGHT?
I'LL TELL MYSELF THAT NO NEWS IS GOOD NEWS
ONION
MELOMASTER
A LONELY SINGLE KANG PIL-GU SOCK
PRICE: 1,000,000 WON
YOU ARE ONE OF THE
FINAL CANDIDATES FOR THIS ROLE.
OUR PRODUCER, MARK JONES,
WILL BE VISITING SEOUL.
SCHEDULE A TRANSACTION
AN APPOINTMENT HAS BEEN BOOKED.
HYEON-JUN & JEONG-SIN
GWON SE-NA ANNOUNCES RETIREMENT
AND LEAVES FOR A FASHION SCHOOL IN THE US
THE END
NICE TO NOT MEET YOU
SCRIPT
FAMILY RELATIONSHIP CERTIFICATE
WIFE: YUN HWA-YEONG,
CHILD: LEE JAE-HA
"ASK ME ANYTHING"
SEONGIL STATION
SPECIAL THANKS TO OH YEON-SEO
FOR HER APPEARANCE
LEE JUNG-JAE
AS LIM HYEON-JUN
LIM JI-YEON
AS WI JEONG-SIN
KIM JI-HUN
AS LEE JAE-HYEONG
SEO JI-HYE
AS YUN HWA-YEONG
CHOI GUY-HWA
AS HWANG JI-SUN
JEON SEONG-WOO
AS BAK BYEONG-GI
NA YOUNG-HEE AS SEONG AE-SUK,
JEON SOO-KYUNG AS OH MI-RAN
JIN HO-EUN AS WI HONG-SIN,
KIM HYUN-JIN AS LIM SEON-U
CHO HEE-BONG AS CEO SON,
KIM PUB-LAE AS CHIEF EDITOR HONG
KIM JAE-CHUL
AS LEE DAE-HO
OH YEON-SEO
AS GWON SE-NA
JEONG EUN-JI
AS AI SU-JI